the second computer that you should buy
the second computer you should buy and
save up your money for is one of these
used Dell Optiplex computers um that you
can run as a server so you go see other
video about the laptop that you want to
put desktop Linux on and get used to
using it maybe several maybe you can put
BSD on there you can put whatever you
want on there that's the whole point
you're not going to break anything
that's you're going to put the different
things on there and experiment but when
it comes to your lab now now you need a
server that lives at home that is being
you know that allows you to log into it
and SSH into it and chop it up into
different virtual machines and that's
these things these Dell Optiplex are
really really useful they're really
cheap and they're extremely fast they
have most importantly they have really
fast DDR Ram H and and fast discs and
what that means is that when you start
to do things like uh containers and
kubernetes and stuff like that um the
speed of the disc is going to be a
limiting factor so buy one of these and
it comes with a keyboard and if you want
to you can buy several of them you
should maybe you can buy three of them
and you can cluster them together Etc uh
as you can see the price tag is still
very very reasonable at $233 for your
second computer so far if you take this
on the laptop that you paid $250 bucks
for now you're still under $600 for two
killer Linux machines that you can
practice and build on you still haven't
even paid you paid less than one three
credit hour course in college by the way
so this is where you should be investing
your money my friends all right